ظآزLove crosses every cycle
of life and deathظآز
ظآزSo let me fall with youظآز
ظآزAll the noise of the mortal worldظآز
ظآزIs nothing compared to her eyesظآز
ظآزWhoever said love itself is sinظآز
ظآزWhen a heartbeat turns into
wind and moonlightظآز
ظآزPainting a banquet
of endless spring bloomsظآز
ظآزHow beautifulظآز
=Blooms for Her=
=Episode 20=
Jinghe.
Are you all right?
Mei Lin,
let me take you home.
Did he force you to marry him?
No.
I agreed to get
(Population and Land Register)
Zhao's population and land records.
Your Highness,
Prince Xuanlie is attacking.
Let's take the rear passage.
Come on.
Mei Lin,
you lied to me.
(Population and Land Register)
Census records?
Coronation ceremony?
It was all a lie.
You only wanted
to trick me
out of Zhao's surrender letter
to curry favor with Murong Jinghe.
Isn't that right?
Yue Qin,
even now,
haven't you woken up yet?
You killed Pei Du.
I should avenge him.
He was forced.
He doesn't deserve to die.
A fallen emperor,
living only to endure humiliation
from all.
That's the best punishment for you.
I understand now.
Just go.
- Go.
Your Highness, we found them!
Well, well, Jinghe.
You've fallen into my hands after all.
Murong Xuanlie,
Zhao's surrender letter is in my hands.
If you insist on killing me,
how will you
explain it to Father?
Prince Jinghe died for the empire
and was killed by Zhao traitors.
That's the best explanation.
Mei Lin,
if you come to me now
and beg me to take you away,
I might spare Jinghe's life
for a few more years.
Murong Xuanlie,
haven't you had enough
of this pathetic show?
In this world,
there's no worse actor than you.
Kill them.
Except for that woman,
kill them all!
Loose!
Leave!
Come on.
No!
Jian!
ظآزMoonlight spills like quiet tidesظآز
ظآزA celestial bird
brushes the mountain's edgeظآز
ظآزWings of light drift through the airظآز
ظآزLike blossoms that refuse to fadeظآز
ظآزIt asks no right or wrongظآز
ظآزNor fears the turning of fateظآز
ظآزA trace of spring on the windظآز
ظآزA whisper of a broken heartظآز
ظآزA farewell song unfoldsظآز
ظآزCarrying every sorrow within itظآز
ظآزKarma weaves its endless threadظآز
ظآزAnd I would follow you
without turning backظآز
ظآزLife and death become
nothing sharp or finalظآز
ظآزLove and hate are carried away
on the breezeظآز
ظآزBefore freedom is ever reachedظآز
ظآزOne must first dissolve into tearsظآز
ظآزLove crosses every cycle
of life and deathظآز
ظآزSo let me fall with youظآز
ظآزAll the noise of the mortal worldظآز
ظآزIs nothing compared to her eyesظآز
ظآزWhoever said love itself is sinظآز
ظآزWhen a heartbeat turns into
wind and moonlightظآز
ظآزPainting a banquet
of endless spring bloomsظآز
ظآزHow beautifulظآز
ظآزTwo hearts leaning into one anotherظآز
ظآزPerfectly, impossibly rightظآز